In terms of the thesis that that, you
know, that I've talked about on this
channel and and what I think's going to
happen. Remember, the stock market will
often have corrections in the back half
of midterm years, and oftentimes the
correction in the stock market will
start in either August or September.
Now, in two of those years, in 2018 and
2014, the stock market started
correcting in September. It wasn't
really obvious that we were in a
correction until October. So, there's no
guarantee that we're going to get into
September and be like, "Oh, yeah, like
this this is what's happening." In in a
couple of those cases, it wasn't really
even obvious that this is what was
happening in in until until September.
If we if I show you the S&P 500 in 2014,
you can see that it it topped the week
of September 15th, right? And and, you
know, we didn't get this big red candle
down until about early to mid-October.
And then if you look at at 2018, you can
see that the market found a top the week
of September 17th, but it was still
basically almost at new highs even the
week of October 1st, right?